Was y'all in the casino together or something?
2人でカジノにいたの？
Yeah, I wasn't even... Like, he lost his money.
ああ、俺は別に…
あいつが自分の金すったんだよ
He was axing, let me tell you what happened.
あいつ頼み込んでてさ
何があったか話すわ
He was axing a f**king lady.
おばちゃんに頼み込んでたんだよ
Like, auntie, auntie...
「おばちゃん、おばちゃん」って
He's calling everybody on his phone. Nobody giving him no bread.
片っ端から電話かけて
でも誰も金貸さねぇの
He's axing the ladies, like, regular people.
普通の女の人たちに頼んでんだよ
Like, they look like they work nine to five jobs, like, not no rich people.
9時5時で働いてそうな
金持ちでもなんでもない人たち
I'm like, you fake tweaking, gang.
「お前ちょっとイカれてんぞ」って
I probably hit him back for it for mad long. You feel me?
で、金のことで
ずっと連絡してたんだよ
It was, I swear to God, everybody probably telling me.
マジでさ、みんなに言われてたんだよ
Everybody telling me, like, yo, bro, he playing with you.
「お前、ナメられてんぞ」って
I didn't even care. I didn't even care.
俺は気にしてなかった
全然気にしてなかった
But then when I fake hit him about it, bro, you fake super tough.
でもちょっと催促したら
あいつ急にイキり出してさ
I'm like, yo, you tweaking, broski.
「お前イカれてんな」って
But was you fake hitting him about it?
軽く催促してたの？
Like, yo, y'all really want my money?
「俺の金どうすんだよ」って？
You sitting here losing everybody else's money.
「人の金ばっかすってんじゃねぇよ」って
No, no, no. I probably, like, got spun off, like, ten times, blah, blah, blah.
いやいや、たぶん10回くらい
はぐらかされてさ
And then one day he was in the strip club.
そしたらある日ストリップクラブで
He just made it rain on everybody.
みんなに金ばら撒いてたんだよ
He made it rain on the whole club.
店中に金ばら撒いてた
That's the worst.
それは最悪だな
Can I tell you something, bro?
ひとつ言っていい？
I don't really like saying stupid s**t, feel me?
バカなこと言うのは
好きじゃねぇんだけど
But when I tell you, bro...
でもマジでさ
Everybody looking at me like, you gonna let him play?
みんなが俺を見て
「ナメられたままでいいの？」って
I'm like, leave him, bro.
「ほっとけよ」って感じ
It's the image. It's the image.
イメージだよ、イメージ
Now, if that story is true, though,
その話がマジなら
it is f**ked up when somebody owe you money
金借りてる奴にそれやられたら
マジでキツいよな
and you like, yo, you, bro, the whole world is telling you.
「おい、お前さ」ってなるし
世間もみんなそう言ってんのに
And at that point, it ain't about the money. It's about the respect.
そうなると金の問題じゃねぇ
リスペクトの問題なんだよ